const NBA = {
  questions: [
    //1
    {
      question: "What NBA team has the most championships?",
      options: [
        "Los Angeles Lakers",
        "Boston Celtics",
        "Chicago Bulls",
        "Houston Rockets",
      ],
      answer: "Boston Celtics",
    },
    //2
    {
      question: "What NBA player has the most championships?",
      options: [
        "Bill Russell",
        "Micheal Jordan",
        "Robert Horry",
        "Karl Malone",
      ],
      answer: "Bill Russell",
    },
    //3
    {
      question: "What is newest NBA franchise?",
      options: [
        "Miami Heat",
        "Memphis Grizzles",
        "Charlotte Bobcats",
        "OKC Thunder",
      ],
      answer: "Charlotte Bobcats",
    },
    //4
    {
      question: "What team was the first NBA team?	",
      options: [
        "New York Knicks",
        "Boston Celtics",
        "Orlando Magic",
        "Detroit Pistons",
      ],
      answer: "New York Knicks",
    },
    //5
    {
      question: "What is the name of the largest NBA arena?",
      options: [
        "Smoothie King Arena",
        "Phillips Arena",
        "American Airlines Arena",
        "United Center",
      ],
      answer: "United Center",
    },
    //6
    {
      question: "How many NBA teams are there?",
      options: ["32", "28", "30", "20"],
      answer: "30",
    },
    //7
    {
      question: 'What is the highest game winning percentage for a season"?',
      options: ["100%", "89%", "87%", "78%}"],
      answer: "89%",
    },
    //8
    {
      question: "Which NBA team has won the most games in history?",
      options: [
        "Boston Celtics ",
        "Golden State Warriors",
        "Washington Wizards",
        "San Antonio Spurs",
      ],
      answer: "Boston Celtics",
    },
    //9
    {
      question: "Which NBA coach has the most wins?",
      options: ["Steve Kerr", "Pat Riley", "Greg Popavich", "Don Nelson"],
      answer: "Don Nelson",
    },
    //10
    {
      question: "Which NBA team is worth the most money?",
      options: [
        "Chicago Bulls",
        "New York Knicks",
        "Los Angeles Lakers",
        "Toronto Raptors",
      ],
      answer: "Los Angeles Lakers ",
    },
  ],
  currentQuestion: 0,
  score: 0,
};
